Here
is [music] a common story in the
insurance world. A client realizes the
value of a specific type of coverage
only after a diagnosis at which point it
is unfortunately too late to add it.
Here I spill the consultation in January
19th, 2026 with [music] a client. Her
breast biopsy results are out. The
result is T2 N1 M0. This means stage 2.
N1 [music] means it has spread to the
lymph nodes but it hasn't metastasized
spread to distant [music] organs yet.
The report of your breast surgery
confirmed an invasive breast cancer
[music] right breast. You are stage T2N1
M0 ER positive [music] PR negative and
her two negative. The good news it
hasn't spread further yet. However,
treatment [music] must start immediately
and the doctor recommends chemotherapy.
Positive note, the patient already has
true health [music] insurance so she can
focus on the medical treatment. Negative
note, the patient must [music] focus on
treatment and can no longer work to
provide for her family despite having
children, parents, and siblings who
depend on her. It all comes down to
money. So, Venry, now that I've just
[music] been diagnosed like this, can I
still buy that critical illness program
you offered me?
>> I'm so sorry, ma'am. If you've already
been diagnosed, especially with cancer,
it's a pre-existing condition and you
can no longer buy it. Please make sure
your current health [music] insurance
policy stays active. Keep up with the
payments so your treatment costs remain
covered, including cancer outpatient
care, and follow-up benefits.